I also was falling in love with someone
我也和那个人坠入爱河
who had a really wonderfully normal, balanced, grounded life
那个有着完美的、安定的、理智的生活的男人
and we decided together that
并且我们一起决定
we wanted our relationship to be private
我们的关系要保持私密
我爱你
Sometimes it is the focus on…
有时候，要专注于…
Sometimes, to all of us, thank you, thank you to the Amazon…
有时候对我们来说，谢谢！谢谢亚马逊！
Taylor Swift! Oh my god!
我的天哪！
我们都知道，William Bowery Joe (霉姐夫全名）
William Bowery Joe, as we know
and Joe plays piano beautifully and he’s always just playing
Joe能弹一手好钢琴，而且他也经常在弹
and making things up and kind of creating things
还会创作音乐
and as I was crazy, cause Joe has written that entire piano part
我真的超级激动，因为是Joe创作了整个钢琴部分
and he was singing the body verse part
而且是他唱的主歌部分
I can see you standing, honey
我看见你站在那里，亲爱的
With his arms around your body
靠在他怀里
Laughing but the joke’s not funny at all
应和着无聊的玩笑
He was just singing it
他就那样唱着
the way that the whole for the first…
就这样，这首歌诞生了…
And, so, I was interest and asked if we could keep writing that one
然后呢，我就很感兴趣，问他我们能不能把这首歌创作下去
and it was pretty obvious that it would be a duet
当然，这明显会是一个二重唱歌曲
cause he has such a low voice
因为Joe的声音很低
and that’s a really good song down there in that register
这真的是一首非常惊艳的歌，尤其是那段的音域
And then we were really, really big body
这是一个很成功的合作
你的爱答不理，让我好厌恶你
我对你恨之入骨
加冰的威士忌，落日的余晖
我找不到你，这令我悲痛欲绝
I just heard Joe singing the entire fully formed chorus of Betty
我还听过Joe唱Betty这首歌的完整副歌部分
from another room
他的声音从另一个房间传来
and I just was like, “hello,”
然后我就探个头来句：“你好呀”
You’re like, “I do this professionally, and…”
你来句：“我可是专业的，而且…"
“Hello,”
"你好！”
“and love the conversation”
“我喜欢这样的对话”
It was a step that we will never taken
这是我们从未迈出的一步
Because why would we have ever written a song together？
就是，为啥我俩要尝试一起写歌呢？
I thought you were doing a bit like Joe and I wrote a song
我觉得你俩那种感觉就像：我和Joe一起写歌
and I thought it gonna be like, you know
然后我觉得那样的话，你知道
like people write 2 songs about their animals, their relationships
俩人一起写两首，关于他们的宠物、他们的感情的歌
and you’re like, no no, it was like a real song
然后你会强调，不不，这是基于现实的歌
So this was the first time that we had a conversation
这是我们第一次关于一起写歌的交谈
when it came and I was like “Okay, this could be really weird,
当这一切发生的时候，我觉得，行吧
and we could hate this
这事可能很奇怪，我们可能会讨厌这样
So, could we just, because…we are in quarantine and there's nothing else going on,
所以，我们能不能，因为被隔离时也没什么别的事
could we just try to see what was it like if we write the song together
我们能不能试一下，看看一起写歌会产生什么样的化学反应
So he was singing the chorus of it
然后他就唱了副歌部分
and I thought it was not a really good sing from a man’s voice
但是吧，我觉得那个部分不太适合男声
from the masculine perspective
就是不适合男性视角
and I really like that it seems to be an apology
我还是很喜欢这听起来有道歉的意味
[Joe戴着一顶棱纹的帽子]
Oh, he played me the scrabble
嚯，这货在玩填字游戏
I’m about to… The type game, no I can wait, I can wait
哎呀我要…打字的游戏，不用，我可以等
It will make him sweat
这会让他浑身出汗的
This game, will get, you know,
这游戏，你知道
he will get stressed and he will,
会让他压力很大，然后他就会说
“What is she playing at? What’s she gonna play?
“她玩啥呢？她下一步要干啥？”
So she’ll gonna get triple work…”
所以她这下得做三倍的工作了“
Yeah, which, you know, it’s not
对啊， 你知道，不知道
[Joe保护Taylor不被狗仔队拍到]
We have hidden lots of different goodies in this house
我们在这个房子里藏了好多好东西
然后89和91这俩挨着
你们都是Janelle Monae的搭档，而且Taylor将会出演新版《猫》
你愿意和他们中的任何一个合作一部音乐剧吗?
A musical? I don’t think I'm quite up to the standard
一部音乐剧吗？我感觉我可能没到那么高的水平
as much as I love it, you know
尽管你知道，我很喜欢音乐剧
你好呀Joe
What's going on Benjamin?
怎么啦本杰明（Taylore的第四只猫猫）？
You’re just a happy little cat
你就是只快乐的小猫咪
好吧，她确实给我男朋友发消息了，但是…
[Taylor在周六夜现场中给Joe唱歌]
[Taylor在亚马逊音乐节里为Joe唱歌]
Gigi: Taylor忍不住一直在看Joe
Ashley: 来，咱发消息告诉他